- Hello . - Wanna have a little fun ?
Who is this ?
Tell me your name and I 'll tell you mine .
I don 't think so .
- What 's that noise ? - Oops . I farted .
I didn 't think you would hear me .
No , that popping noise .
Oh . I 'm making popcorn . I 'm getting ready to watch a video .
- Ooh . What is it ? - It 's just a scary movie .
Do you like scary movies ?
- What 's your favourite ? - Mm , I don 't know .
Think .
Oh , I know . Kazaam . You know , the one where Shaq plays a genie .
That 's not a horror movie .
Yeah , well , you haven 't seen Shaq act .
- Hey , you have a nice voice . - Thanks .
You never did tell me your name .
Why do you wanna know my name ?
Because I wanna know who I 'm looking at .
What did you say ?
Nice breasts .
Look , what do you want ?
I wanna see what your insides look like .
Well ... Well , then , turn to page 54 .
Oh .
Hey , nice .
Listen , asshole , you 've had your fun , now you better stop or else .
Or else what ?
Or else my boyfriend 's going to be here any minute ...
and he 's black and he 'll kick your ass .
- Oh , really ? - Yeah .
You mean the one who wears make-up and dresses like a woman ?
- How did you know ? - Turn the porch lights on .
Help . Help .
Oh , that 's not my boyfriend .
I mean , I 've fucked him a couple of times , but that 's it .
Look , I 'm calling the cops .
Go ahead . Call the cops .
But you might wanna check the back door first .
You forgot to lock it .
Take that , you psycho .
I can 't feel my legs .
I think my arm is broken .
- Sorry . - I want my mummy .
Hello , Drew .
Oh , God .
No .
Daddy . Daddy .
Daddy , no . No .
- Did you hear something ? - No , I didn 't hear anything .
Bobby , what are you doing ? My dad 's in the other room .
It just occurred to me I never
climbed through your window before .
Yeah , well , now that you got it out of your system , Bobby ...
- What ? - You have to leave .
Why ?
Come on .
What 's going on in there ?
Ow . Daddy 's head is stuck . Unstick Daddy 's head .
- Dad , can you knock ? - Knock ?
I thought I heard screaming in here .
No . No , you didn 't , Dad .
Well , it could 've been that crack I smoked earlier , I guess .
- Yeah . - Yeah , yeah , that 's what it was .
Listen , I got to leave town for a couple of days . Okay ? No big deal .
Just , you know that new business I started with those Colombian guys ?
Oh , you mean Uncle Escobar . Yeah .
Yeah . Yeah , that 's right .
Well , there 's a problem . Some money went missing .
And apparently , some legs are going to get broken .
It 's just better if I lay low for a couple of days .
Okay .
Now , if the cops raid the place ...
I never heard of you .
- And don 't forget ... - To flush your stash .
Oh , you are my little girl . I love you so much ...
that I left you a little something in the coffee can .
Dad ...
But you have to remember to step on it before you sell it .
Now , what are you going to cut it with ?
Baking ...
- Baking soda . Not baking powder . - Soda .
Because baking powder guys will have
muffins growing out of their nose .
Dad .
You love that joke , don 't you , honey ?
You 've loved that joke since you were two years old .
- Okay , well ... - Okay , I love you .
- I love you . - Have a good trip .
- Bye . - Bye .
Is the coast clear ?
Oh , Cindy , that nightgown .
That was close . God .
I was , home watching The Exorcist , and it got me thinking about you .
If this is about the time I puked green
slime and masturbated with a crucifix ...
It was my first keg party , Bobby .
No . No . It was edited for TV . All the good stuff was cut out .
So you thought you would just climb through my window ...
and we would play bump-bump ?
Oh , I was kind of hoping to get my balls licked , but ...
I wouldn 't wanna break your little underwear rule , now , would I ?
So maybe just some on-top-of-the-clothes-type stuff ?
Okay . But just for a minute .
What the ...
Wrong set .
Bobby . Oh , Bobby .
I don 't wanna wait
For our lives to be over
- No , Bobby , don 't . - Ow .
Jeez . I see , yeah .
Yeah , my dad .
Okay , stud , you have to go now .
Oh , about the sex stuff ?
I was only half serious . I mean , I don 't wanna rush you or anything .
Hey , would you settle for PG-13 ?
What 's that ?
Oh , jeez .
Good night , Bobby .
Shorty , you are so loud .
And make sure you take your behind to class today .
- I do be going to class . - Lunch is not a class , Shorty .
It is when you got the munchies .
See , that 's why you such a dumb-ass .
Your mother .
You my brother . That 's your mother too , jackass .
Oh , yeah . Well , then , your father 's stupid .
So ? I don 't know him .
Yeah , me neither .
- Hey , girl , you ready ? - Yeah , in a minute .
- Come on . We 're going to be late . - Ooh , wait . There 's Buffy .
I don 't know why you hang out with her .
- She is such a ho . - Why do you say that ?
Because I 've seen her .
My friend Sean had a pool party this summer .
Sean ?
You know , Puff Daddy ?
Anyway , everybody was drinking Cristal champagne .
And then it started to get wild , and people
was getting freaky in the pool and stuff .
I look over and there was your girl
getting buck wild in the Jacuzzi .
So ?
With a backup dancer .
I mean , that 's nasty . That 's lower than the security guard .
At least security can get you backstage . She don 't love herself .
Bye , Daddy .
I don 't know . I think Buffy 's sweet , Brenda .
Oh , she is as fake as Press-on nails .
- Hey , baby girl . - Hi .
- Hi . - What is up , my sister ?
- Bye , Mr Gilmore . - Bye .
- Is he gone ? - Yep .
Do you like what you see
It 's all about the money
- Hey , Cindy . - It 's the only way to be
- I love this colour . - Let me see that .
Oh , you guys should not use this brand .
Why not ?
Because they test their products on animals .
So ?
Look , have you seen what they do to those poor animals ?
Well , I am much more of a people person .
I 'd like to feed all the hungry little children of the world .
I 'd much rather help my fellow man than some animal .
Spare a dollar ?
- Oh . Get away from me , you bum . - Buffy .
Can 't you see he 's just hungry ?
Here you go , sir . A nice sandwich for ya .
- See ? - I said a dollar , bitch .
Ow .
God . Look at this place .
It 's a circus .
Hello . I 'm Gail Hailstorm , author of the book You 're Dead , I 'm Rich .
A small college town is in shock ...
after the unthinkable has happened :
a brutal killing spree that left one teen dead ...
That 's it . Two teens dead ...
and this small town shaken and stirred .
It 's times like these ...
Police are combing the area for clues .
It seems there are no witnesses available at this time .
There are no suspects in custody . Police
are asking anyone to come forward .
Reporting live for Black TV . White folks are
dead and we 're getting the fuck out of here .
- Let 's roll , Jack . - Right .
Come on . Grab your shit and let 's go , motherfucker .
Go . Go .
Hey , do you think the press is going to wanna talk to us ?
Girl , no . The press only wants to interview
the most ignorant person they can find .
I 'm on TV . Oh , shit . First Cops , now this .
Oh , man , I 'm going to be a star , son .
- What can you tell us about Drew ? - Well , she had the phat ass , son .
I mean , it was like bang .
How close were you to the victim ?
Real close . Until the roofies wore off .
Then she woke up talking about pressing charges .
So I just pulled my tongue out of her ass and left .
What would have been your last words to Drew ?
Run , bitch . Run .
Hey , yo , dog . Does this shirt make me look gay ?
No , man .
What about now ?
Nah .
- Cool ? - Yeah .
Here . Take one , guys . Don 't forget : election 's Tuesday .
" Don 't forget : election 's Tuesday . "
Goddam it . Son of a bitch .
What 's the matter , honey ?
My report card .
Well , at least you got one " A. "
- Yeah . I did , huh ? - Yeah .
You 're so smart .
- Hey , has anybody seen Bobby ? - Nah .
You know what ? That kid is always late .
I don 't get it . He lives so close .
Why are you
Any better than anyone else
Why are you so good
- See you later , Hairy Mama ... - Bye , hon . - Bubba , Jim ...
Big Jim , Little Jim , Slim Jim , everybody .
Bye .
I 'll see you later . Ciao , Ding . All right .
Damn , girl .
I 'd sure like to get in them pants .
Really ?
Yeah . What size are these ?
- Hey , guys . - Hey , Bobby .
Hey , baby .
- How you doing ? - Good .
You guys see all the reporters out there ?
Yeah .
Yeah . Saying that girl Drew Decker got killed last night .
I know .
You know what ? I think I knew her .
Really ?
Yeah . She had a brother named Steve ?
Yeah .
Long hair , pretty little mouth , perfect ass ?
- That was her . - Nah , I was talking about Steve .
Whatever happened to him ?
Hey , do you guys think it 's strange that she got killed ...
exactly one year after we ...
you know , killed that guy ?
Hey . Cindy , that was an accident .
Was it , Greg ?
- Yeah . - Yeah .
Would you look at what they 're doing ?
When are we going to do stuff like that , huh ?
One day .
- You like that , baby ? - Yeah , that 's different .
- You like that ? - Oh , I love that .
Oh , I love when you play with my ass .
I 'm not playing with your ass .
- Ray . - Oh , my bad .
Come on , man . Hey , Bobby , put on some music .
Hold on . Here , put this on .
Yeah , that 's the shit right here .
It 's raining men
Hallelujah - It 's raining men
- Baby . - Amen
- I wanna go out - What ? - I 'm going to let myself get
- What ? It 's a classic . - Absolutely soaking wet .
Turn on the radio , man .
Yeah . Whoo .
- What ? It was laundry day . - What the fuck is ...
Yeah .
Whoo . Yeah .
- Hey . Come over here . - What ?
Just get a little closer to me .
Something you 're going to tell me ?
Bobby , what are you doing ?
I just want you to touch it . Just touch it . Come on .
Just a little bit . Come on .
- Whoo . - Everybody wants you
- Ow . - Oh .
Yeah , that 's what I 'm talking about .
- Bobby . - Oh , my God . Shit .
God , Cindy ... Oh , shit .
Oh , my God . What was that ?
I think we hit something .
Oh , man .
Bobby , look at my car , man . My dad 's going to freak .
I didn 't see it . It came out of nowhere .
- Oh , my God , we hit a boot . - Where 's the foot ?
I don 't know .
Where the ...
- It 's a body . - Oh , shit . Is he alive ?
- I don 't know . - Well , check it out .
I can 't .
- Shit . - Oh , my God .
- We have to call the police . - No way . I ain 't going to jail .
- We have to . - Hey , Cindy .
Do you know what they do to young boys in prison ?
You know , all those sex-starved convicts
just waiting for a fresh piece of meat .
Hey , you 're right , Cindy . Maybe we should call the police .
Oh , yeah . That 's a great idea , Ray . But what about
Brenda , huh ? You think she wants to go to jail ?
This is manslaughter , okay ? We 're all going to fry for this .
- We 're looking at 10 to 15 years . - Shut up , Bobby .
- Alcohol all over ... - It 's okay . I 'm fine .
We 're in so much trouble , you guys .
I 'm fine .
Don 't blame that shit on me , Ray .
Look , we ... We 'll get rid of the body .
Unnecessary .
- Now you 're thinking . - We 'll dump him in the ocean .
Not the ocean , the pier .
- Guess I 'll be leaving now . - That 's a great idea .
- What about the alcohol ? - We 'll get rid of it .
Come on . It 'll be all right .
- Come on . Hurry up . Let 's go . - Put him in the trunk .
I won 't have anything to do with this .
Shut up .
Cindy , come on . We 'll just pretend it never happened .
You know , like the time we got drunk
and we went down on each other .
I 'll get his arm .
- I 'll grab his other arm . - I 'll grab his ass .
We 'll take him down to Williamson Cove and we 'll dump him in there .
The sharks 'll take care of the evidence .
Oh , my God , someone 's coming .
- Oh , shit . It 's Shorty . - Brenda , take care of him .
Shorty , I know you ain 't driving without no papers .
I got papers , blunts , bongs ...
all the ingredients to make a high nigga pie .
- Hey , yo , can I help you ? - Yo , what 's up , Ray ?
Yo , son , you all need jumper cables ?
Nah , we 're cool .
Oh , good , because I left my roach clip at home .
- Go home , Shorty . - Yeah , I 'll see you later .
- Peace , Ray . - Get the trunk closed .
- It won 't close . - I 'll do it .
Hold on . Hold on . Put him down . He 's heavy . Oh , God .
Jesus . Okay , look . On three we dump
him over the ledge , all right ?
Wait , wait , wait . Shouldn 't we at least check his wallet ?
- For what ? - Shit , he might have some money .
We already committed murder . We might as well rob his ass .
I 'll take the credit cards .
- I want his jewellery . - I 'm going to take his drawers .
Get off . Hey , yo , get off . His drawers are mine . Hey , yo .
- I got me a gold ring . - Credit cards .
All right , let 's get him in the water .
I don 't think I can , Greg .
- It 's not too late . - Shut up , okay ?
Christ , already . I 'll do it .
- Come on . - Just get him in the water .
Okay . One , two ...
three .
Right now we make a pact . We take this to our grave . Agreed ?
- Agreed . - Agreed ?
- Agreed . - Say it , Cindy . Say it .
We take this to our grave . Say it .
Greg , chill . Come on . You 're hurting her . Greg .
- Come on . - We take this to our grave . Ow .
And we never mention this again .
- Mention what ? - The guy we just killed .
Well , you just mentioned it , Greg .
Starting now .
- Stupid bitch , man . - God , I hate him .
It 's going to be okay , baby . It 's going to be okay . I promise .
Just touch it again . Come on . Please ?
You have to move on , Cindy . That 's all behind us now .
Exactly .
- It 's a coincidence . - Greg 's right , Cindy .
I mean , what do you think we 're in , a horror movie ?
Yeah , you guys are right . I mean , if we were ...
they 'd probably cast some dingbat like
Jennifer Love Huge Tits to play me .
Yeah , yeah , or they 'd ... or they 'd cast people in
their late twenties , early thirties to play us .
Kenny , get the camera ready . Here . Hold my gum .
Hi . Sheriff , Sheriff , can I get a statement ?
No comment .
Damn . Who do I have to screw around here to get a stupid story ?
Hey . Hey , no running .
Loser .
- Slow it down . - Blow me .
All right .
Hi . Gail Hailstorm . Field Reporter , Hard Story .
Special Officer Doofy .
Oh , hi , Doofy . Doofy , listen . Is there a problem on campus ?
- No comment . - Okay . - No comment . - Okay .
You know , you look awfully young to be a police officer .
Yeah , I 'm 25 and a half years old .
Ooh .
- Yeah , that 's this many . - Ah , so big .
Yeah . That 's big .
Well , you don 't look a day over 12 .
Except for the big head and glazed-over look in your eyes .
- Ooh , was that drool ? - Yeah . I forgot to swallow .
Don 't worry , because I never forget .
Would you remind me not to do that again ?
Sorry .
Hello . Due to the recent tragedy , the
sheriff and me , your principal ...
will be questioning all students throughout the day .
Wow . Sounds like we 've got the makings
of a serial killer on our hands .
Yeah , I 'm not supposed to say . It 's official police business .
Hey , Doofy , what do you say you and
I go inside my van over there ...
and , get to know each other a little better ?
- Would you like that ? - That van ?
Yeah , that van right there .
Yeah . Yeah , okay , let 's go . Come on .
Oh .
A terrible tragedy and an unbearable loss .
It 's days like today that we need prayer in school .
It starts to unravel the very moral fabric of our society .
Here you go , baby .
You go to your daddy .
- I 'll see you after class . - Sweet . - All right .
Okay , class , who would like to give
their oral presentation first ?
- Anybody ? - Yes .
Anybody else ?
- Okay , Heather . - Oh , yes . Okay .
- Okay . Can I start ? - Yeah .
Okay , my presentation is on the First Amendment .
And it began on May 25 , 1787 in Philly with George Washington .
And it states , and I quote ...
" When our Founding Fathers argued the
passage of our glorious Constitution ... "
And so , the First Amendment gives
us the right to say what we want ...
Oh , shut the fuck up .
So , who 's next ?
Cindy Campbell .
Isn 't she the daughter of , well , you know ...
- Oh , yeah , you know , old Mrs ... - Old Mrs ...
And , yeah . Yeah , the one and only ...
The one and only .
- Why , hello , Cindy . - Hi , Principal Squiggman .
Thanks , Doofy .
It 's Special Officer Doofy today , Cind .
Now , Cindy , Sheriff has some questions
that he would like to ask you today .
What is that , that god-awful smell ?
I don 't know .
I got a poopie .
Did you just say that you , you went poopie ?
- Yeah . It was good . - Mm .
- Get him out of here . - Yes .
- Thank you , Doofy . - Okay .
You should now go back to Special Ed .
Okay . Salute .
Maybe a change of underwear , son .
- Bye , Doofy . - Bye , Cind .
- How are you , Cindy ? - Fine .
- How are you , Sheriff ? - Bloated , constipated .
Got a boil on my ass the size of a walnut . You know , the usual .
Cindy , I want to ask you some questions about Drew Decker .
- I didn 't really know her . - Oh , come on . Sure you do .
- No . I mean ... - Come on .
I didn 't really know her .
I 've been in this game a long time . Don 't
bullshit a bullshitter , all right ?
Tell me about Drew . What was she like in bed , Cindy ?
Tried to get you . It 's an old police trick .
It 's an old police trick . You didn 't
fall for it . Good for you , kid .
Hike .
Pass . Pass .
- All right , shower up . - Yes .
Yo , Dugan , man , nice play , yo . Word up .
Johnson , what a block , baby . Word up .
Thanks a lot , kid .
Woodward .
- Hey . Hey . - Nice ass .
Damn .
Hey , yo , Greg , man , what 's up ? You going to hit the showers or what ?
No , man . I think I 'm going to work out ,
you know , beat the bag a little .
Suit yourself , kid . All right . Last
one in the shower 's a rotten egg .
Come on , you all . I 'm going to get you all .
Don 't let Uncle Ray catch you .
Who did this ? Huh ? Where are you ?
This isn 't funny , all right ?
A small dick 's like a disability , man .
Huh ? Would you make fun of a guy in a wheelchair ? Huh ? Would you ?
Come on out here , you sick fuck .
I 'll kick the shit out of you right now . All right ?
It 's not the size of the hammer ,
it 's the nail you 're throwing it at .
It 's a shame how she died , you know ? She was such a nice girl .
Yeah , she used to baby-sit my brother Doofy .
- He had the biggest crush on her . - Ray , you 're a dead man .
Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey , hey , hey , hey .
No , no , no , what you trying to say ?
You wanna get butt-naked and wrestle ?
Chill out . Chill out . Chill out .
- Bring it on , Ray . - Hold my earrings .
- Chill out . - Where 's my Vaseline ?
- Take it easy . - What 's the problem ?
I 'll show you the problem .
Oh ... That 's you ?
They ... They turned the hot water off in the showers , all right ?
Oh , shit .
Oh , yeah . Laugh it up , you guys . Big laugh .
You know what ? You can all go to hell .
Greg , you 're not the only one who got one .
Oh , you mean Bobby 's got a baby dick too ?
No . I was talking about the note .
I got one too .
- Somebody knows . - That 's bullshit , Cindy .
Look , someone 's just trying to fuck with us , you guys .
We have to call the police , Greg .
You call the police , and I 'll kill you myself .
You 're hurting her , man .
And you know what ? That goes for all of you guys .
That psycho wants a piece of me , bring it on .
But I 'm not going to jail . You got that ?
What 's everybody talking about ?
Just forget it , Shorty . You already know too much .
Aren 't they beautiful ?
- Buffy . - Contestant number one .
Very good . And contestant number two .
Very good . And contestant number three .
- Buffy . - That 's my girl .
- That 's my girlfriend . - Yeah , that 's my girlfriend too .
- Hey , kiss my ass . - Yeah , I 'm hitting that too .
- All right , Buffy . - Hey , shut the hell up , man .
Oh , yeah , man . Best pussy I ever had .
What , you want a piece of me ?
Now the talent portion of the competition .
Oh , you guys , I 'm going to go downstairs for a closer seat .
Let 's begin ...
with contestant number three ...
See you after the show . Buffy Gilmore .
Hey , you know what ? I 'm going to go , hit the
head . You want me to bring you back anything ?
No , no , no . I 'm good , man . But hurry
back . She 's going to perform .
- Don 't worry . I 'll be back . - So , good evening , Buffy .
And what will be your talent for this evening ?
Acting . I 'll be doing a dramatic reading .
Buffy Gilmore doing a dramatic reading .
Hey , do that thing from Baywatch . She 's running down the beach .
Look out , Greg . Look behind you .
- It 's him . It 's the killer . - Huh ?
Oh , my God . Somebody do something .
Somebody do something .
He 's killing him .
- He 's killing him . - Must be an original piece .
She 's good . She 's good .
- What 's wrong with you people ? - That 's fantastic .
You fucking bastards . Why won 't anyone help ?
Amazing .
- She 's the next Pamela Lee . - God .
Oh , God . Oh , God . Don 't .
Greg , hold on .
Give it up for Buffy Gilmore . Wonderful .
Absolutely fantastic .
I think we have a winner , ladies and gentlemen . Miss Buffy Gilmore .
Buffy , wait . You have to go back onstage .
- No . I have to get to Greg . - But you won .
- They 're calling your name . - There 's a killer ...
- I won ? - They 're calling your name . Go .
Buffy , what happened ? What about Greg ?
Oh , fuck Greg . I won .
- Congratulations . - Oh , out of my way , loser .
Miss Buffy Gilmore .
Here she comes Miss Teen She 's So Fine
Such lovely tits - Give me my crown , bitch .
And a great behind
There she is Doggy style anytime
And I 'll do her behind behind and behind
Oh , there she is
She loves 69
- There 's no sign of him anywhere . - He could 've taken the body .
That 's impossible , Cindy . There 's no
blood . There 's nothing . Look around .
I bet it 's just Greg playing another one of his dumb jokes .
He 's going to turn up . I 'm sure of it . He 's probably at my house ...
waiting for us right now , you guys .
All right , fine , fine . But you know what ?
I 'm going to look around some more , so ...
You mind catching a ride home with Buffy ?
Yeah , no problem .
- All right , fine . - Call me later .
- Hello ? - Hello , Cindy .
- Who is this ? - It 's me , Bobby .
You know , your boyfriend .
Yeah , I 'm sorry . I guess I 'm a little jumpy lately .
- Hey , any sign of Greg ? - No .
- Do you want me to come by ? - No .
I 'm just going to take a bath , and then I 'm going to go to bed .
Okay . I 'd really like to see you , but ... I love you .
Aw . I love you too , baby .
Bobby , I told you ...
I still know what you did last Halloween .
Who is this ?
Ow . Ow .
- Hello . - I 'm going to kill you .
- I 'm going to slice you up . - Who is this ?
I 'm going to chop you like liver .
What do you want ?
I 'm in the house .
Do you know where I am ?
I could be anywhere . I 'm like the wind , baby .
Yeah . Where am I ?
You 're-you 're behind the couch .
- What ? How do you know that ? - I can , see your feet .
Ah . Okay , turn around .
Close your eyes . No peeking .
Yeah . No . No . No .
Hey , hey , hey . No peeking . No peeking . Turn around .
Good .
Okay , now you can look .
Now do you know where I am ? You don 't .
No , Mr Killer . I don 't know where you are .
I 'll give you a big clue .
Oh . I got to stop drinking .
- Grandma . - Ow , baby . Ow . Ow . Oh , my hip .
Come on .
White woman in trouble off the 744 ...
- Are you okay ? - Oh , my God .
I heard screaming . What 's going on ?
Bobby , he was here .
- The killer was here , Bobby . - It 's okay .
- I can explain that . - Oh , my God .
A friend gave them to me . Cindy . Cindy .
Cindy . Cindy . Cindy .
Cindy . Cindy .
It 's me , Cind .
Cindy , you know me . Cindy .
I know you 've had a rough night , Cindy , so I won 't keep you .
I just want you to look at some photos . Tell me what you think .
- No ? - No .
- I 'm sorry , Sheriff . - You sure ?
Okay , you 're free to go . Do you have somebody picking you up ?
- Yeah . - Oh . Just ...
Just check that one out again .
Mm , no .
No ? No ? All right . Well , worth a shot . All right , thanks .
Guess what I just did with those hookers we busted .
No way .
All the way , man . Yes , yes . Watch this . Watch this . Doofy .
- Yeah ? - Come on . Come on .
Okay .
Special Officer Doofy reporting .
Hey , Doofy , smell my fingers .
What 's that ?
That 's when you know you 've become a man , Doofy .
Hey , Terry , smell my finger .
- What the hell is that ? - My ass .
- Get the hell out of here , Doofy . - Doofy .
Mum said get home now .
Tell Mum I 'm on official police business .
Cindy , are you okay ?
Hey , hey , hey . No talking to the witness .
Go get in the car , Doofy . She 's coming with us .
- Does Mum know ? - Yeah , Doofus .
Mum says when I wear this badge ...
you 're supposed to treat me like a man of the law .
Yeah , well , Mum also said for you to stop
sticking your dick in the vacuum cleaner .
Okay , three , two ...
- Oh , no . Gosh darn . - What now ?
No , it 's just that there 's all these numbers with deci ...
What , can 't you count ?
No , I can count , but there 's really ...
Here , let me make it easy for you . Chump-zilla , listen up , okay ?
This little piggy went to the market . All
right ? This little piggy stayed home .
Now , if this little piggy doesn 't roll the goddam camera ...
I 'm going to put my foot up his fucking ass ...
We 're live , Gail .
Gail Hailstorm standing out front of the police station ...
where I 'm going to try and get a glimpse of Cindy Campbell ...
the young girl who was attacked earlier this evening .
You 're on my foot , fat shit .
- Sorry , G ... - What did I say ?
Huh ? What did I say ?
" Don 't ... Don 't ever step on Gail 's shoes . "
- Why not ? - Because Gail wears Prada shoes .
- You idiot . - I 'm a ... I 'm a bad man .
- Cindy . Cindy . - How about one minute ?
Cindy , can we get a statement ?
Buffy Gilmore , Miss Teen . She 's not talking .
Is it true the police have someone in custody ?
Come on , Cindy .
Cindy , Cindy , your ass looks fat .
Bitch .
- Good shot . - Come on .
- All right , who copped a feel ? - Gail , it was me .
- Oh , my God . - It was an accident , Gail .
I only touched it , the top of the breast .
- It was so tender and juicy . - Shut up .
Yo .
Hello , Shorty . What are you doing ?
Nothing . Sitting here watching the game . Smoking some bud .
Are you all alone ?
- Wassup ? - Wassup ?
What the ... Who 's that ?
Yo , pick up the phone .
- Wassup ? - Wassup ?
Yo , Dookie , pick up the phone .
- Yo . - Wassup ?
- So what you doing , son ? - Nothing . Just chilling , killing .
True . True .
So you think Bobby did it ?
I don 't know . But he was there , Buffy .
I knew there had to be something . He 's just too perfect .
Handsome , smart , good in bed .
What did you say ?
Hey , Cind . Got your ice pack for your hand .
- Ow . - Sorry .
I 'll get you one for your head .
No , no , that 's okay , Doofy .
Hey , we 're going to get that guy you dumped in the water . Yeah .
I 'll be next door if you need me .
Night , Cind .
Buffy , you told him ?
The moron overheard a conversation Greg and I were having .
Yeah , but what if he says something ?
Who 's going to believe a retarded retard like him anyway ?
Don 't worry .
Cindy , telephone .
Thank you .
- Hello ? - Hello , Cindy .
- Guess what . - No .
- You got the wrong guy . - No .
- Yep . It 's not Bobby . - Doofy ?
- Who is this ? - Doofy . Doofy .
- Doofy . - Oh , my God .
Hello ?
I said don 't disturb me when I 'm cleaning my room .
I heard Bobby got out this morning .
I haven 't seen him around . Is he pissed ?
You mean since you branded him the Candyman ? No . His heart is broken .
Yo , son . It 's like I seen this all before .
They had a killer at your old high school , Shorty ?
No , it was in this movie Scream . Same dialogue and everything .
- This is ill . - How did it end ?
I don 't know . Some niggas started shooting up
in the movie theatre , so we just broke out .
No doubt .
Okay , I say we all just stick together .
Tonight everyone meet at my house . And bring some friends .
But don 't tell everyone , okay ? Try to keep it quiet .
Okay . Yo . Party at Cindy 's house .
Drunk white women for everybody .
Ray , if you see Bobby , tell him I love him .
Okay . If I see Bobby , I 'll tell him I love him .
Jesus .
It 's okay . It 's all right . It 's just me , baby .
What , you don 't still think it 's me , do you ?
No .
It 's just that somebody did try to kill me .
Yeah .
And the police said I scared him away .
I know . He called me last night .
Yeah , so you see , it couldn 't have been
me . I was in jail last night . Remember ?
You 're the best .
I 'm sorry . Please understand .
Understand what ? That my girlfriend would
rather call me a killer than touch me ?
That 's not true , Bobby .
- Then what is it ? - What is it ?
She 's gone and she 's not coming back .
It 's been over a year , Cindy .
But Ginger was such an important part of the Spice Girls .
- Oh , you got to move on , baby . - Oh .
I am sorry if my complicated life ...
is an inconvenience to your perfect existence .
Cindy . Cind .
Okay , everybody , listen up .
Let me just say ...
the killing of these ... these teenagers has been tragic , but ...
Hey , you know , shit happens .
- Sheriff . - Sheriff .
Yes , Miss Thunderstorm .
Have they found Cindy Campbell 's father ?
- No . - Isn 't he a suspect ?
That is classified information . Where are you getting that ?
I 'm sorry , but , my sources are strictly confidential , Sheriff .
Hey , Gail .
Gail swallows .
Watch this .
Hello ? Who is this ?
What ? You wanna kill me ?
Oh , God . Hold on .
Cindy , it 's for you .
All right , knock it off , Buffy .
Now , as you all have heard , there is a killer in our town ...
and the police have asked us to
give you the following safety tips .
Stay in well-lit areas .
Do not travel alone whenever
possible . Always wipe front to back .
And remember , never , ever believe someone ...
when they tell you that shaving your pubic hair ...
will rid you of crab infestation .
Now , I understand this is a difficult
time for you young ladies .
So if anyone needs to come to my office to talk ...
I am here for you .
- What a crock of shit . - It 's not , Buffy .
He 's real .
Miss Mann ?
Come in , dear . Have a seat . Take off your bra if you 'd like .
No , thanks .
What can I do for you , Cindy ?
I need to talk . See , I have this problem ...
and I don 't know who to tell .
- Not feeling so fresh ? - Huh ?
Feminine odour and itching got you down ?
No . No , not that .
Then what is it ?
I have a terrible secret .
Well , Cindy , we all have our little secrets .
Sometimes we do things we 're not so proud of .
Some for money ...
others to gain the athletic edge on the competition .
Sometimes those secrets come back to haunt us .
- Do you know what I mean ? - Yes , I do , Miss Mann .
Thanks for ball ... I mean , all your help .
I have to go to class .
Anytime , dear .
Buffy , are you coming ?
I 'll catch up with you guys in a sec .
Redrum .
Hello ?
Somebody there ?
Hello .
Very funny . Who put you up to this ? Cindy ?
Lose the cape . It 's way too ' 90s horror .
Oh , so what movie is this from , Die , Cheerleader , Die ?
Wanna play psycho killer ? Can I be the helpless cheerleader ?
Oh , so this is where I 'm supposed to beg for my life ?
Please , Mr Killer , don 't kill me .
So is this where I 'm supposed to bleed ?
Oh , look , I 'm bleeding . Eek . Eek .
Oh , yeah , I 'm supposed to run , right ?
Okay . I 'm running . I 'm running . Help .
Help . Oh . Now I 'm going to fall and
break my leg , leaving me helpless .
There you go , Mr Scary Killer . I 'm panicking now .
Oh , God . Somebody please help me .
Oh , God , no .
No .
Oh , now what ?
I guess this is the big climax . Hope you don 't mind if I fake it .
Oh , look at me . I 'm all dead .
I 'm a gross , scary severed head . Come on . Please .
Do you know who I am ? I 'm Miss Teen .
You 're really giving me a headache .
And you got blood all over my Gucci sweater .
I hope you 're going to pay for that .
Ah . I will not be ignored by the likes ...
- I 'm going to jump . - Phil , get back in there .
- No . - What are you doing up there ?
- Be reasonable . - I can 't take this fucking job ...
or those greasy shithead teenagers any more .
I 'm going to end it all .
Wait . Hold on . We 're getting help for you .
Now we know Bobby 's not the killer . So who is ?
I don 't know .
Well , if the killer was in your house last
night , why didn 't he just kill you then ?
Because he 's just messing with us .
Don 't you see ? He 's got us right where he wants us .
We can 't go to the police . He 's just out
there watching us and waiting for us .
What are you waiting for , huh ?
What are you waiting for ?
- What am I waiting for ? - What are you waiting for ?
Fuck you .
Oh , my God .
Ray , I still don 't think this party is a good idea .
You know I 'm not going to let nothing happen to you .
I just don 't feel right .
Why can 't we just do something else ?
Okay . How about we go to the movies ?
Huh ? You like that ? See a little movie , huh ?
Yes . Yeah .
- Hey . That is my song . - Hey .
You know they gave me a shout-out on the album , right ?
What ?
Yes .
♪ Everywhere I go I see the same ho 's ♪
Ooh , Brenda .
Did I tell you how sexy you look in my jersey ?
- I do , Ray ? - Yes .
I like it . Hey , get up . Go-Go over there . Let me see it .
Ooh . Yes , I like that .
You like that ? You like that ? You like that ?
Yeah . Hey .
Hey , put this on with it .
Ray , you are so freaky .
That 's right . You know I 'm freaky , girl .
Go on . Pull it . Pull it up .
Yeah . Here , here . Put this on with it .
Go on .
- Are you sure ? - Go on , girl . Go on . Pull it on .
- Okay . - Go on .
- I like that look . - Ooh . I 'm bad .
Ah , yes . Here . Put this on with it .
Go on , girl . Put it on .
Yeah . Put that shit on there . Come on . Just shove it on .
Do it . Yeah . Ooh , so fucking sexy .
Come here , girl . Bring your little sexy ass over here . Come on .
Full speed . Charge .
Yes . Yes . Come on . Turn around .
Turn around . Come on . Yes , Brendan .
Take it , Brendan . Take it , Brendan .
Who ?
Brenda . Come on , come on . Put the helmet on .
No , let 's role-play . Come on . You get me .
- Get me . Come on . Come on . - Huh ?
I 'm here at Lover 's Lookout .
It 's dark , it 's in the middle of nowhere ...
and it 's where hormone-driven teens
love to come and fool around .
So very likely we 're about to see someone get killed .
Okay , sure enough , there 's a girl in
that car , blouse unbuttoned , all alone .
Let 's see if she 'll have a word with us .
Hi . Gail Hailstorm , author of the new book You 're Next .
- Oh , yeah . - Can you tell us your name ?
Well , my name 's Heather .
Heather , can you tell us what you 're doing out here all alone ?
Well , yeah , sure . My boyfriend and I were just , like , making out ...
and then we heard a noise out there ,
so he went to go check it , but ...
Well , that was , like , ten minutes ago or so .
Yeah , yeah .
Heather , has it crossed your little mind
that your boyfriend was probably murdered ...
and you 're about to be slaughtered next ?
Really ? No way .
Way . Heather , good luck .
Okay , thanks , Gail . You 're the best .
I know . Just as I thought . The murder is happening as we speak .
I 'm going to try and break into the
bloodshed . Are you getting this ?
Excuse me . Heather , Heather , can you
tell us what you 're feeling , honey ?
Lots of pain . Gail , please help me . Gail , please .
I 'd like to help you out , kid , but it 's sweeps .
Sir , sir , can I get a word with you ? Sir .
You got a lot of nerve coming here .
I 'm just trying to do my job .
Get the camera off me now . You 're dead , bitch .
No , Kenny , keep rolling . Keep rolling .
I 'm going to slice your head off and shove it up his ass .
Sweet Jesus . Shit .
Get , get that camera off me .
Oh , my God , Kenny . Kenny , move your fat ass .
Kenny . Oh , my God , he 's right behind you .
This man is chasing me , Gail .
I am so scared right now .
I just want to say ...
to the family of my cameraman , Kenny ...
I am so sorry .
This was my interview ...
my story .
It 's all my fault .
You want some popcorn ?
I brought me a little snack of my own .
- You want some chicken ? - Nah .
For all you all talkers up in here ,
it 's time to keep it down right now .
Back at you .
Why they acting already ? It ain 't nothing but the previews .
The largest ship the world had ever known .
Its 400 passengers and crew on a
maiden voyage to a brave new world .
A journey that would change their lives forever .
I 'm the king of the world .
Amistad II - Get your ass back down there , boy .
I 'm going to go to the bathroom real quick .
Don 't leave now . The movie 's about to come on .
I got to go to the bathroom . Here . Take your hot sauce .
Hurry up , man . Don 't be long .
Back up . Let him through .
You can move back some . You don 't own the theatre .
And they 're off . It 's number three in
the lead . Number two close behind .
And number three is the winner .
Number two has placed , and number four to show .
Next week 's Triple Crown starts at 2 : 30 . Be here early .
Hey , who is that ?
Go ahead . Do it again . Do it again .
Anon .
Don 't go in there .
Lord , I 'm going to have a heart attack .
Damn , this is some scary shit .
Oh , I am scared .
Excuse me .
I think I paid my money like everybody else up in here .
- Out of her favour where I am ... - That ain 't no man .
You can see her real hair right there .
Do you mind ?
I know you better get out of my face .
Out of my face . Out of my face .
This is all me up in here . You handle that .
- Will you shut the fuck up . - Yeah .
This movie is good . Hey , baby .
You came back just in time .
She 's about to get it on with Shakespeare .
- He found out she 's a girl . - Shut up .
Yeah , I got you . I got you on camera .
You on Candid Camera now .
You ain 't know that .
Hello . Hey , girl . I 'm in the movie . Huh .
Shakespeare In Love . . Ooh . You lying .
For Christ 's sake , will you just shut your trap .
- Shut up . - Hold on .
I don 't know why you all is acting like this .
My girlfriend already seen the movie . She said
they don 't even stay together in the end .
Give me that .
Right on .
Will you sit down ?
Shut up .
Your ass is grass .
- This is for Thelma . - And Louise .
This is for talking through The Fugitive .
- You ruined Schindler 's List . - All Jackie Chan movies .
- Boogie Nights . - And Big Momma 's House .
And I cannot marry the daughter of Sir Robert De Lesseps .
You guys , there 's a , there 's a few too many people .
Oh , hi . Please don 't , don 't ... No . Hey , you guys , stop .
Hey . Hey , please . That 's my dad 's .
- No , don 't touch ... Ah , ah , no . - Do you have more beer ?
- Do you have more beer ? - No . Yeah . Check in the garage .
No , no , no , no , no . Don 't .
Kitty , you scared me .
Horsey . Oh , you scared me too .
Hello ? Who 's there ?
Oh , my God . Oh , my God . Please , don 't .
Please . I 'm just a day player .
Oh , my God .
Chug . Chug . Chug . Chug . Chug . Chug . Chug . Chug .
Yeah . Yeah .
Oh , Bobby . Bobby . I was worried about you .
I thought the killer got to you before I could .
Could what ?
I wanna go upstairs . There 's something I wanna show you .
- Yeah . - Oh , yeah .
- Hey , party on . - Yeah .
- So ... - So .
Here we are again .
Yeah .
And , you know , if you 're not ready ...
I 'll understand .
Bobby .
I am ready .
- You are ? - Yeah .
I can 't keep fighting these urges .
I have to just give in to them ...
and let them flow .
Right .
Bobby ?
I have been so selfish .
This is like a scene from a movie or something .
Only it isn 't a movie , Bobby .
This is real life .
It 's all a movie , baby .
There 's the sound guy . There 's the
script supervisor . How ya doing , baby ?
- Bobby ? - What ?
What I mean is that in real life ...
you have to enjoy each moment .
Bobby . Bobby .
Can I tell you a secret ?
Sure , man .
I see dead people .
Man , this shit is awesome .
Yo , son , you got to roll some more of that shit .
Ah , shit .
We don 't have any more papers , man .
We don 't have any more papers .
Aw , man . What can we use to make a bong ?
Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke .
- Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . - Yeah .
Oh , shit , son .
Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke .
Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke . Toke .
This some good shit .
Bobby . I 've never done this before .
Come on .
It 's okay . It 's okay . It 's just like ...
It 's like sucking on a Tootsie Roll Pop .
- A Tootsie Pop ? - Yeah , a cherry-flavour one .
- Oh . - With the fudge in the middle ?
- Okay . - Show me now
Show me how
How it feels when we 're together .
Just like that .
- I 'm afraid if we wait - Just like that , baby .
♪ We 'll be waiting till forever ♪
Oh . Jesus .
I never could wait to get to the chewy middle .
- You know what ? Let ... Let me . - Oh . Okay .
Goddam .
♪ I 'm on a rocket ship to a mother ship ♪
♪ I 'm flying solo but don 't know if I can stop ♪
♪ Don 't ask me why don 't make me lie ♪
♪ Just kick back just sit back ♪
♪ Enjoy the ride ♪
♪ Because I 'm a spaceman ♪
Guess it 's been a while .
♪ Asking me out stay with me ♪
It 's very , ' 70s of you .
♪ Stay with me tomorrow 's just ♪
Oh , yeah . Oh , Bobby .
Come here , Bobby . I want it now .
Oh , man , am I fucking stoned .
- Yeah , me too , son . - Hey .
Hey , you guys hear that ?
- Hello ? - Hello .
Hello ?
What 's your favourite scary movie ?
I 'm going to gut you like a pig .
Oh , yeah . Oh .
Yeah . What 's my name , Bobby ?
What ?
- What 's my name , bitch ? - Ow . God . It 's Cindy .
Whose is it , Bobby ? Whose is it , Bobby ?
It 's yours .
Oh , my God .
Oh , shit .
♪ Don 't even contest because I 'll make you undress ♪
♪ Like porn dancers waiting at the front door for an answer ♪
♪ Hey , yo , I 'm sick of artificial mcs like silicone titties ♪
♪ Hey , yo , check it , yo . Fuck a cheap bong ♪
♪ I wanna smoke cheech and chong ♪
♪ And if I wanna fuck long I let my ding-a-long hit the bong ♪
♪ And then the song always pass the dutchie to the left ♪
♪ Because the right way is wrong ♪
I got one . I got one . I got one . Here it goes . Ready ?
♪ I 'm going to slash and gash cut another hole in your ass ♪
♪ I spill blood on the walls then play tennis with your balls ♪
♪ If the phone rings don 't answer the call ♪
♪ Going to slit your throat fuck you like a goat ♪
♪ Peel your foreskin off and make a winter coat peace ♪
Yo .
That was the illest rhyme I ever seen , son .
Bobby , where were you tonight ?
- What ? - I was just curious .
What took you so long to get here ?
Why are you so curious ?
I don 't know .
I thought it would fit the ' 90s horror cliché if ...
you turned out to be the killer .
Oh , so , what ? You think I killed Buffy and Greg ?
Buffy and Greg are dead ?
- I thought you knew that . - Oh , my God .
Bobby , turn around . It 's the killer .
Cindy .
- Oh , my God . Bobby . Bobby . - Cindy . Help me .
- Bobby , it 's okay . - Gimme the gun . Gimme ...
It 's going to be okay , Bobby .
Yo , wait for me . There 's a killer in the house .
There 's ass , blood and guts everywhere .
Someone done gone crazy , son .
We all go a little crazy sometimes .
Bobby , no .
Oh , shit , son .
Oh , my God .
Cindy , he shot me in the lungs .
You wanna hit this shit ?
Ketchup .
Just like my mum puts on her spaghetti , baby .
Oh , my God . Ray , you 've got to help me . Bobby 's gone crazy .
Surprise .
Surprise , Cindy .
Why are you doing this , Bobby ?
Why ? Why ? You hear that , Ray ?
I think she wants a motive .
- Did Scream have a plot ? - No .
Did I Know what You Did Last Summer make any sense ?
Don 't think so . And what about the sequel ? Huh ? What
the hell was with that fat , white Jamaican kid ?
Oh , I wanna kill that motherfucker .
I know . Me too , man . It was bad casting , Bobby .
How about this for a motive ? Lack of sex .
It can cause serious deviant behaviour .
- I thought you loved me . - Oh , I did , baby .
I did . But abstinence can make you
discover new things about yourself .
That 's right , Cindy . I 'm gay .
And in case you haven 't noticed , so is Ray .
What ? I ain 't gay .
What are you talking about ? You took me to that club .
So ? They play good music .
What about our trip to San Francisco , then ?
I wanted to go shopping .
But you made love to me .
No . First of all , you sucked my ...
Whatever , Ray . I don 't want to talk
about this now . The point is , Cindy ...
that I 'm a new man , and I 'm ready to leave
all this behind and start a new life .
- So you killed all your friends ? - Oh , no .
Just you . And maybe Shorty ...
but that wasn 't planned or anything .
But here 's the genius part .
We 're copycatting a serial killer that already exists .
- It 's the perfect crime , Cindy . - But wait . There 's more .
Hang on to your seat , baby , because this one 's a screamer .
- I 'll be back . - Oh .
Move your big ass . Come on .
Dad .
What are you going to do , frame him ?
Nah . We 're just having a little bit of fun with old daddio .
The police are going to find you and daddy both dead ...
and me and Ray are the only survivors of a maniac 's revenge .
- You ready ? I 'm ready . - You ready ? I 'm ready to do this .
All right . Let 's do this , Ray .
Let 's do this . I 'm ready to do this shit .
- Come on . Come on . All right . - All right . All right .
Come on . Come on .
Give it to me . Give it to me . No .
- Wait , wait , wait , wait . - All right .
Ready ? You ready ? All right . Let 's do this .
Wait , wait . Ready .
- Come on . Come on . - Ready .
Come on . Give it to me . Give it to me .
No . Wait , wait , wait , wait , wait . Just ...
You remember what we talked about ?
I know , man . How many times we going to go over this ?
To the side , right ?
I know , okay ? Stop . Just ... All right .
Okay . All right . I 'm ready .
Trust me , okay ? I got this shit . Ready ? Come on .
Wait , wait , wait . I just don 't know ...
What the fuck . I 'm about to cut your throat , boy .
Okay .
Stop acting like a little girl . Come on . Come on .
You 're right , you 're right , you 're right , you 're right . I 'm ready .
Come on . You ready ?
You guys are psychos . You 've seen one too many TV shows .
No . Watching television shows doesn 't create psycho killers .
Cancelling TV shows does .
The Wayans Brothers was a good show , man .
It was a good-ass show , and we didn 't even get a final episode .
Take it easy . I 'm feeling a little woozy here .
It 's my turn . Give me the knife .
Fuck out of here . Ain 't nobody stabbing me .
Surprise , Cindy .
All right , all right . Hold on a second .
Just give me a moment . Ah . One ...
Oh , yeah . That 's it .
Ah . Okay .
Dad . Are you okay ?
I thought I told you not to have a party unless I was here .
But , Dad , you were here . You were in the closet .
Oh , yeah , that 's right . Did you get
some girlfriends ' numbers for me ?
Dad , they 're dead .
Ah , you know , I can 't get a break .
What 's that ? Is that the cops ?
Okay , okay , listen , honey . Help me up now .
If the cops come , tell them I 'm a plumber , okay ?
You had a leaky faucet , and you called , and they
sent me over . We don 't even know each other .
No . No .
Dad , Dad , put your arms down .
What the hell 's going on here ?
Sheriff , it 's a bloodbath in there .
- He was right here . I swear it . - Who was ?
The killer . The guy that murdered all my friends .
And the sick bastard planted drugs all in the house there .
- All over the place . - Dad . Stop it .
All right , Cindy . I 'm going to have
to take you down to the station .
I 'm cool , though , right ?
- I 'm okay ? - Let 's ... Let 's go , Cindy .
Cindy . Call me . Call me .
Daddy 'll get you out , honey .
Okay . Let 's go over this again .
- You say it was an accident . - Yes .
He was on the road .
And you think he came back to get revenge ?
It has to be him , Sheriff .
Here , Sheriff . They wanted me to give this to you .
- That 'll be all , Doofy . - Okay .
I 'm going to go , then .
- All right . - All right .
Bye , Cind .
I 'm sorry , Cindy . It wasn 't the man you guys killed .
His name was David Keegan . Some fishermen
found his body a few weeks later .
He 's buried in Lakewood Cemetery .
That 's impossible .
Then I don 't know who it could be .
He 's got to be someone ...
who was connected with all the victims ,
someone who knew about the accident .
Someone who could move around without being noticed .
Oh , my God .
She used to baby-sit my brother Doofy .
He had the biggest crush on her .
It 's me , Cind .
' Night , Cind .
- Doofy . - Shithead ?
- Have you seen Doofy ? - No .
- Have you seen Doofy ? - No , Sheriff .
- Has anybody seen Doofy ? - No .
Yeah . Just went out the back , Sheriff .
Doofy .
♪ He walks alone under the big city lights ♪
♪ He always knows just when the time is right ♪
♪ He never shows what he 's thinking he keeps it inside ♪
♪ Because he 's too cool for school ♪
♪ He comes alive when the sun goes down ♪
♪ He gets it right you know he 's always down ♪
♪ He 's got one eye open and his ear to the ground ♪
♪ And he 's too cool for school ♪
♪ He 's an operator he 's a real player ♪
♪ And if you mess with him you know you 'll never win ♪
No .
Shit , son . Yo , what the deal ?
Yo , if you all watching this tape right now ...
that means I didn 't make it .
Either I 'm a prisoner , or worse , dead .
But either way it goes , I 'm going to tell you
all the rules to survive this situation .
Rule number one : You got to be quick .
Rule number two : Don 't fall down .
And rule number three : Whatever you do , never look back .
You all wish me luck .
Snatch and run , you all .
Come back here , you motherfucker . You son of a bitch .
♪ You all want drama wanna make a scary movie ♪
♪ Rappers coming in with their team and carry toolies ♪
♪ You can jump right out of the screen and barely move me ♪
♪ We hard hitting , directing and starring in it ♪
♪ You all want drama wanna make a scary movie ♪
♪ Rappers coming in with their team and carry toolies ♪
♪ You can jump right out of the screen and barely move me ♪
♪ We hard hitting , directing and starring in it ♪
♪ Bad ♪
♪ The bad ♪
♪ The evil , the evil ♪
♪ Put them together ♪
♪ Two times ♪
♪ Slim Shady ♪
♪ Royce the 5 '9 " ♪
♪ Na , na , na , na I 'm going to slash and gash ♪
♪ Na , na , na , na , put another hole in your ass ♪
♪ Spill blood on the walls and play tennis with your balls ♪
♪ If the phone rings don 't answer the call ♪
♪ I 'm going to slit your throat fuck you like a goat ♪
♪ Peel your foreskin off and make a winter coat ♪
♪ I 'm a Denny 's surprise I 'll scoop out both of your eyes ♪
♪ Na , na , na , na , scrape the meat off your thighs ♪
♪ Leave your carcass for flies because ♪
♪ Everyone who meets up with me ♪
♪ In the end , eventually dies ♪
♪ I 'm the last thing you see I 'll hang you from a tree ♪
♪ Scare the shit out of you then watch you pee ♪
♪ I 'm a bad ass killer ain 't nobody iller ♪
♪ You 're ice cold thriller because I 'm the fucking chiller ♪
♪ I 'm the bad ass killer there ain 't nobody iller ♪
♪ I 'm going to slice and dice because murder 's my vice ♪
♪ Stab you once or twice maybe even thrice ♪
♪ Care initials in your liver make you quiver ♪
♪ Deliver yeah , that 'd be nice ♪
♪ I 'll dissect your heart rip your entrails apart ♪
♪ Hack off your head and that 's just a start ♪
♪ I 'll put the scary , scary movie make people do a dooby ♪
♪ Make them pee-pee up the place when they see my ugly face ♪
♪ You better keep alert or you 'll be sleeping in the dirt ♪
♪ I got a phd in how to use my cutlery ♪
♪ I make you kneel and squeal as I turn you to a beal ♪
♪ You 'll be squirting in your shorts ♪
♪ And you 're squirting crimson quarts ♪
♪ I 'll chop the virgin beaver with my shiny butcher 's cleaver ♪
♪ Need your cries of fear it 's music to my ears ♪
♪ I cut off oscar Meyer 's weiner I stick it in a bun ♪
♪ Slap on some pickle relish ain 't we having fun ♪
♪ I 'm a bad ass killer there ain 't nobody iller ♪
♪ You 're ice cold because I 'm the fucking chiller ♪
♪ I 'm the bad ass killer there ain 't nobody iller ♪
♪ I 'm going to cleave your gut treat you like a slut ♪
♪ Mutilate your organs and shove them up your butt ♪
♪ I 'll slit you ear to ear you know what ♪
♪ Then I 'll slam a beer ♪
♪ Saw off your toes jam them in your nose ♪
♪ Cut your tongue out feed it to a trout ♪
♪ Fry them in a pan shoot it out my can ♪
♪ Aim it at your face then you 'll know your place ♪
♪ I promise you pain I 'm totally insane ♪
♪ Now let me tell you once again ♪
♪ I 'm the bad ass killer there ain 't nobody iller ♪
♪ You 're ice cold because I 'm the fucking chiller ♪
♪ I promise you pain I 'm totally insane ♪
♪ I promise you pain ♪
♪ Like a scrotum here it is in a nutshell ♪
♪ 1972 ♪
♪ That 's the year I got here when my dear mother 's water blew ♪
♪ Not really realising the prize that 's been begot her ♪
♪ The bona fide lo-fi high-octane philosopher ♪
♪ The genius with a penis the few , the proud , the me ♪
♪ I liked me so much I had to buy the company ♪
♪ Soul for sale sold to Satan for a hell of a lotta luck ♪
♪ I 'm hard to come by like a straight guy working at Starbucks ♪
♪ Thank the thinkers that think they thunk the thoughts that theorised ♪
♪ Idolised or despised bet I 'm getting recognised ♪
♪ Mount rushmoure it , no , ignore it , can 't rock with no big head ♪
♪ Half the people want me half the people want me dead ♪
♪ I am the angel of def with my rhymes against humanity ♪
♪ Teeter-tottering between brilliance and insanity ♪
♪ The one part the Fuehrer the one part the Pope ♪
♪ It 's the inevitable return , baby of the great white dope ♪
♪ Conclusions you drew proportions you blew ♪
♪ Lost son of iggy false bigger nose than ziggy , true ♪
♪ Yes , my name is Jimmy pop no , my pop 's name is dick ♪
♪ Don 't admit to kick it , slick you thick derelict critic ♪
♪ Put down for missed note put up with misquotes ♪
♪ Don 't want the whole story should have bought the cliff notes ♪
♪ Like finger-painting 101 give me no credit for having class ♪
♪ One thumb on the pulse of the nation ♪
♪ One thumb in your girlfriend 's ass ♪
♪ Written on , written off scoff , calling me a joke ♪
♪ I don 't think that I 'm a sell out but I do enjoy coke ♪
♪ I struck gold but never took it for ♪
♪ Granite that 's how I planned it so can it ♪
♪ Around the planet fans demand it and you 'll never understand it ♪
♪ When I die , no lie plan on mass pandemonium ♪
♪ They may display my brain in a picklejar at the Smithsonian ♪
♪ The one part the Fuehrer the one part the Pope ♪
♪ It 's the inevitable return , baby of the great white dope ♪
♪ One part the Fuehrer one part the Pope ♪
♪ The inevitable return of the great white dope ♪
♪ Great white dope great white dope ♪
♪ Great white dope ♪
♪ Yeah , yeah ♪
♪ Hey , yo , we run these streets putting on the great city ♪
♪ You all niggas still pretty just so you all can feel ♪
♪ Feel me , feel me , feel me ♪
♪ We dealing with my thug strictly make ♪
♪ Some noise if you running with me ♪
♪ Do it wild and you know we get busy just so you all can feel ♪
♪ Feel me , feel me , feel me ♪
♪ Say one for the radio two for the pin eye ♪
♪ Wrote the rhyme with niggas coming tight semi ♪
♪ My keys for the three now you suckas fuck with it ♪
♪ More chasing on your ass than the cops who got acquitted ♪
♪ Making rapper 's noise like it was tax season ♪
♪ Selling it back getting paid to crack thieving ♪
♪ Tim 's and Gina , me and my tight jimma up on a track ♪
♪ Make them shake like somebody built a fina ♪
♪ Mo ' money , you barely got toll money ♪
♪ Vocal coach and still roll funny ♪
♪ Thug the fuck out punch lines are killing ♪
♪ Say some other shit really hurt a rapper 's feelings ♪
♪ Who know the outcome must be the wild one ♪
♪ Selling their backs it didn 't even make the album ♪
♪ Feel this bitch as I go for the three ♪
♪ Now fuck onto the game make the game come to me now ♪
♪ Hey , yo , we run these streets putting on the great city ♪
♪ You all niggas still pretty just so you all can feel ♪
♪ Feel me , feel me , feel me ♪
♪ We 're dealing with my thug strictly ♪
♪ Make some noise if you running with me ♪
♪ Do it wild and you know we get busy just so you all can feel ♪
♪ Feel me , feel me , feel me ♪
Yeah , feel me , fool .
I feel you , dog .
This isn 't easy for me .
I know we 've been together a long time ...
but I found somebody else .
Okay ? I 'm in love .
Don 't look at me like that .
We could still be friends .
You can come into my room whenever you want .
We just can 't ... No .
No .
Okay , just one time .
Yeah . That 's it .